The Guide to the Hiteman Leather Company records, 1898-1968
Hiteman Leather Company records, 1898-1968
- "Carlisle Shoe Co.": Correspondence, invoices, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- "Carlisle Shoe Co. Orders": Orders, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- "Carmo Shoe Manufacturing Co.": Orders, Correspondence, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- "Coal": Correspondence, enclosures, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- "C": Correspondence, orders, enclosures, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- "William P. Davidson": Correspondence, orders, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- "William P. Davidson - Orders": Orders, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- "Thomas Dorrity": Correspondence, sales reports, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- "Dept. of Labor, New York State": Correspondence, reports, bulletin, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- "D": Invoices, orders, correspondence, enclosures, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- "Employers Mutual Liability Ins. of Wisconsin": Correspondence, reports, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Untitled: Workman's compensation reports, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- "Employers Mutual Liability Report": Claim reports and enclosures, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- "E": Correspondence, invoices, enclosures, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- "Feakes Mercantile Agency": Reports, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- "F": Correspondence, enclosures, orders, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- "Ganey, Hagan & Co.": Correspondence, handouts, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- "General Information": Rates and schedules, inventory report, product report, other reports, 1960-1962 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- "G": Invoice, correspondence, orders, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- "Thomas Hartnett": Correspondence, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- "Thomas Hartnett - Orders": Orders, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- "Hospital Plan, Inc.": Correspondence, enclosures, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- "Hide Sheets": Reports, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- "H": Orders, correspondence, reports, enclosures, leather samples, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- "Hiteman Leather Co., Inc. West Winfield, N.Y. Boiler and Pressure Vessel Insurance Proposal": Report proposal, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- "I": Orders, invoices, correspondence, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- "J": Shipping enclosures, industry bulletins, correspondence, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- "Kaufman Trading Co.": Auction results, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- "K": Correspondence, Kiplinger letter, invoices, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- "L": Orders, correspondence, invoices, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- "Metropolitan Life Ins. Co.": Claim forms, correspondence, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- "Milligan & Higgins": Bills of lading and weight receipts, correspondence, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- "Marine Midland Bank & Trust Co.": Correspondence, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- "M": Correspondence and enclosures, orders, weight receipts, bills of lading, newsletters, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- "Mc": Correspondence, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- "N": Correspondence, orders, newsletters, enclosures, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- "O": Correspondence, enclosures, orders, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- "P. O. Box Rent, Ins. Registered": Receipts, record of meter readings, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- "Inactive Piecework Rates": Schedules, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Untitled: Piecework schedules and descriptions, 1955, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- "P": Orders, correspondence, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- "Q": Correspondence, orders, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- "R": Orders, correspondence, enclosures, drawing of hide house, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- "Remittance": Receipted statements, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- "S": Orders, correspondence, bills, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- "Tanners' Council of America (Tanners Council News)": Newsletter, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- "Tanners' Council of America": Council handouts, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- "Tanners' Council of America (trade survey bureau 1962)": Reports (Box 12, Folder 50)
- "Remittance: Statements, adding machine tape, correspondence, receipts, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- "Absentee Report": Report, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- "Wires": Copies of telegrams, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- "Letters to All Agents: Correspondence, sales information, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- "American Appraisal": Confirmation, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- "Alpine Leather Company": Correspondence, orders, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- "Alpine Leather Co. - Orders": Orders, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- "Aulson Tanning Machinery Co.": Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- "A": Correspondence, invoices, leather samples, reports, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- "V.J. Barsotti": Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- "Parker Bowman": Notes, correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- "Parker Bowman. Orders": Orders, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- "Sidney Brown": Correspondence, memos, orders, invoices, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- "B": Correspondence, orders, reports, newsletters, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- "Carlisle Shoe Company": Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- "Carlisle Shoe Company - Orders": Orders, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- "Carmo Shoe Manufacturing Co.": Correspondence, orders, invoices, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- "C": Correspondence, orders, enclosures, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- "Wm. P. Davidson": Correspondence, orders, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- "Wm. P. Davidson - Orders": Orders, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- "Dept. of Labor, New York State": Reports, correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- "Department of Labor (Nature and Experience Rating Charges Charts)": Reports, 1961-1963 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- "Thomas Dorrity": Correspondence, sales reports, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- "D": Orders, correspondence, enclosures, leather sample, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- "Trucking Concern": Brochures, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- "Inventory": Rough figures, 1949-1958 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- "Commission Paid": Contracts, weight sheets, invoices, shipping information, 1963-1965 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Untitled: Storage and sales records, 1962-1964 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- "Mohawk Valley Wool": Sales receipts, correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Untitled - loose papers: Accounts, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- "Nick Beucher & Sons": Weight sheets, invoices, diagrams, 1957-1962 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- "Misc.": Inventory, correspondence, invoices, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- "Chester Packing House - Comm. Paid": Receiving slips, invoices, summary, 1959-1962 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- "Swift, Milwaukee Howard Dietrich & Son, Inc.": Purchase and shipping information, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- "Davis Leather. Aschheim": Correspondence, invoice, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- "H. Elkan & Co.": Shipping notices, invoices, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- "Eden & Strass Company": Sales information, 1961-1962 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Untitled [Eden & Strass]: Shipping notices, invoices, correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- "Eden & Strass Comm. Paid": Shipping records, invoices, correspondence, summaries, 1959-1962 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- "Estra Trading Company": Shipping records, invoices, monthly summaries, 1960-1962 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Untitled [Eden & Strass, , Inc.]: Invoices, delivery records, summaries; 1959-1961 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- "H. Elkan & Co. Comm. Paid": Receiving slips, summaries, invoices, 1958-1962 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- "Employers Mutual Liability Ins. Co. of Wausau": Correspondence, reports forms, bill, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- "Employers Mutual Liability Report": Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- "E": Orders, invoices, reports, correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- "Feakes Mercantile Agency": Reports, shipping memo, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- "F": Invoices, shipping memos, orders, newsletters, correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- "General Information": Inventory reports, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- "G": Correspondence, orders, invoices, enclosures, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- "Thomas Hartnett": Correspondence, sales reports, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- "Thomas Hartnett - Orders": Orders, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- "Hospital Plan, Inc.": Correspondence, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- "Hide Sheets": Reports on skins in inventory, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- "H": Sales reports, water pollution information, correspondence, orders, invoices, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- "I": Correspondence, orders, invoices, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- "J": Orders, enclosures, invoices, correspondence, bulletins, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- "Kaufman Trading Co.": Reports - results of calfskin auctions, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- "K": Invoices, reports, correspondence, enclosures, credit memos, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- "L": Orders, invoices, correspondence, enclosures, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- "Marine Midland": Correspondence, bank newsletter, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- "Metropolitan Life Insurance Co.": Correspondence, reports, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- "Milligan and Higgins": Correspondence, weight receipts, bills of lading, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- "Mike Marrone: Correspondence, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- "M": Orders, invoices, correspondence, reports, leather sample, newsletters, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- "N": Orders, newsletters, notices, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- "O": Orders, correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- "P": Orders, reports, correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- "P.O. Box Rent, Ins., Registered": Receipts, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- "Q": Orders, correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- "R": Correspondence, orders, newsletters, reports, enclosure, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- "S": Correspondence, enclosures, orders, leather sample, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- "Tanners' Council of America (Trade Survey Bureau)": Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- "Tanners' Council of America (Past Due Accounts)": Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- "Tanners' Council of America": Reports, bulletins, correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- "Tanners' Council of America (Tanners Council News)": Newsletter and reports, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- "Miss Marianne Tater": Correspondence, reports, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- "Time Studies: Trimming shrunken grain adjustment sheet; plating rates; other rates, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- "Town and Country Shoes": Correspondence, invoice, orders, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- "T": Correspondence, orders, adding machine tapes, invoices, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- "U": Orders, invoices, correspondence, enclosures, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- "Al Verdekal": Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- "V": Invoice and correspondence, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- "Water Pollution": Report reprint, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- "A.L. Webster": Hide market report, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- "W": Correspondence, orders, invoices, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- "X-Y-Z": Credit bill, order, note, correspondence, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- "Wires": Telegrams, notes, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- "Letters to All Agents": Copies of Correspondence, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- "American Appraisal Co.": Correspondence, bulletins, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 47)
- "Aulson Tanning Machinery Co.": Correspondence, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 48)
- "Alpine Leather Co.": Correspondence, orders, invoices, leather swatches, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 49)
- "Alpine Leather Co. - Orders": Orders, correspondence, leather samples, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 50)
- "A": Correspondence, orders, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 51)
- "Bills of Lading": Shipping orders, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 52)
- "Parker Bowman": Notes, orders, invoices, correspondence, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 53)
- "Parker Bowman - Orders": Orders, invoice, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 54)
- "U": Correspondence, orders, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- "V": Correspondence, tax bill, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- "A.L. Webster": Newsletters, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- "W": Correspondence and orders, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- "X-Y-Z": Correspondence and purchase orders, 1962-1964 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- "Remittances": Original and 4 made - vouchers, receipted bills, some correspondence, adding machine tapes, 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- "Remittances": Original and 5 made - vouchers, bills, accounts, etc., 1964 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- "Notice to Employees": Company notices, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- "Wires": Western Union telegrams", 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- "Remittances": Original and 2 made - bills, remittances, some correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- "Remittances": Original and 3 made - bills, vouchers, mail insurance receipts, some correspondence, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- "A": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- "Parker Bowman - Orders": Orders, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- "Parker Bowman": Handwritten notes, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- "Sidney Brown": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- "B": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- "Carlisle Shoe Company Orders": Orders, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- "Carlisle Shoe Company": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- "C": Correspondence and enclosures, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- "Wires": Western union telegraph forms re ordering and shipping, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- "A": Correspondence, orders, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- "Parker, Bowman, Orders": Completed order forms [possible destruct], 1964 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- "Parker Bowman": Notes, Correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- "Sidney Brown": Orders and correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- "Mr. Richard Bertsch": Correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- "B": Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- "Carlisle Shoe Company": Correspondence and orders, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- "Carlisle Shoe Company, Orders": Completed order forms [possible destruct], 1964 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- "Carmo Shoe Corp.": Correspondence and orders, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- "C": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- "Davidson Orders": Orders, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- "Department of Labor Federal": Correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- "Dixon-Bartlett": Correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- "Dept. of Labor, New York State": Correspondence and forms, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- "D": Correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- "Employees Mutual (Reports)": Workmen's compensation claims, doctor bills and correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- "E": Correspondence, bills, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- "Feakes Mercantile": Newsletter, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- "Foreign Correspondence": Correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- "F": Correspondence, orders, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- "Ganey, Hagan & Co.": Correspondence and enclosures, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- "General Information": Inventory reports, 4-63 to 12-63, correspondence; sales and purchases 12-63 to 1-61, 1961-1963 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- "G": Correspondence and enclosures, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- "Thomas Hartnett": Correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- "H": Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- "In Process Inventory": Figures, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- "I": Correspondence, damage claims forms, enclosures, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- "J": Correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- "Kauffmann Trading": Results of auctions, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- "K": Correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- "L": Correspondence, purchase orders, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- "Marine Midland": Correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- "Metropolitan Life": Correspondence, forms, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- "M": Correspondence and enclosures, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- "Mc": 1 piece correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- "N": Correspondence, newsletters, orders, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- "O": Correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- "P.O. Box Rent, Insurance": Receipts, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- "P": Correspondence, newsletters, orders, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- "Q": Correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- "R": Correspondence, orders, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 42)
- "S": Correspondence, orders, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- "Tanners' Council News": Newsletters (weekly), 1964 (Box 17, Folder 44)
- "Tanners' Council of America - Past Due Accounts": Reports, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 45)
- "Tanners' Council of America. Trade Survey Bureau": Reports, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 46)
- "Tanners' Council of America": Reports, some correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 47)
- "Marianne Tater": Correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 48)
- "Time Studies": Studies, raw data, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 49)
- "T": Correspondence, orders, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 50)
- "William P. Davidson": Correspondence and orders, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- "Davidson Orders": Orders, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- "Department of Labor. Nature of Experience Rating Charts": Notices of Experience Rating Charges, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- "Department of Labor New York State": Newsletter, forms, reports, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- "Dixon-Bartlett": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- "D": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- "Employers Mutual (Reports)": Workmans compensation reports, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- "Employers Mutual Ins. Co.": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- "E": Correspondence and orders, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- "Feakes Mercantile": Newsletters, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- "F": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- "G": Correspondence and orders, 1962-1964 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- "Thomas Hartnett": Handwritten correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- "Hula": Forms and correspondence re unemployment insurance case, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- "H": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- "I": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- "J": Correspondence, orders, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- "Kaufmann Trading": Newsletter - aunction results, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- "Kernan & Kernan Willis Morgan": Correspondence and income tax records reproduced, 1962- (Box 18, Folder 19)
- "K": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- "L": Correspondence, orders, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- "Marine Midland": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- "Metropolitan Life": Correspondence and enclosures, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- "Milligan & Higgins": Orders, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- "M": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- "Mc": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- "N": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- "O": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- "P": Correspondence, newsletters, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- "Q": Correspondence, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- "R": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- "S": Correspondence, orders, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- "Tanners' Council of America Past Due Accounts": Newsletter, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- "Tanners' Council of America": Correspondence, reports, newsletters, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- "Tanners' Council News": Newsletter, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 35)
- "Time Studies": Rough drafts - studies, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- "Tanners' Council of America - Trade Survey Bureau": Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 37)
- "Marianne Tater": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 38)
- "T": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 39)
- "U": Correspondence, orders, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 40)
- "V": Correspondence, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 41)
- "A.L. Webster": Market report, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 42)
- "W": Correspondence, orders, 1962-1964 (Box 18, Folder 43)
- "X-Y-Z": Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 44)
- "Wires": Telegrams, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- "American Appraisal": Clients' Service Bulletins, letters, 1963-1965 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- "Aulson": Letters, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- "A": Misc. letters, order forms, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- "Parker Bowman": Correspondence, order acknowledgements, bills, leather sample, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- "Parker Bowman Orders": Order forms", 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- "Sidney Brown": Office memos, bills, purchasing orders, correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- "B": Correspondence, bills, orders, trendletters, tanners forum report, the Analyzer, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- "Foreign Correspondence": Correspondence, shipping orders, bills, purchase orders, 1961-1965 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- "Carmo Shoes": Bills, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- "Coal": Correspondence, salesmemo, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- "Carlisle Shoe Co.": Correspondence, invoices, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- "Carlisle Shoe Company Orders": Orders, correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- "C": Correspondence, bills, orders, clients' service bulletin, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- "Department of Labor - New York State": Employers reports, labor market letters, correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- "Department of Federal Labor": Notes on firing - actual report filed in Department of Labor file (#15), 1965 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- "Dixon-Bartlett": Correspondence, orders, bills, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- "William P. Davidson": Orders, correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- "D": Bills, orders, correspondence, advertisements, invoices, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- "Employer's Mutual (Reports): Accident reports, disability/workmen's compensation reports, employer's mutual reports, correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- "Employer's Mutual Insurance Co.": Safety and health service report, correspondence, accident-investigation report, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- "H. Elkin": Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- "E": Correspondence, invoices, orders, bills, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- "Feakes Mercantile Agency": Reports, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- "F": Correspondence, invoices, bills, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- "G": Bills, accounts, correspondence, invoices, orders, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- "General Information": Pamphlets, correspondence, skincharts, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- "H": Orders, correspondence, bills, 1961-1965 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- "Thomas Hartnett": Correspondence, orders, bills, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- "Hospital plan": Correspondence, bill, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- "In-Process Inventory": Inventory, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- "I": Bills, invoices, correspondence, 1958-1965 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- "J": Orders, bills, invoices, correspondence, price guide, advertisement, notice, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- "Kaufmann Trading": Correspondence (results of auctions), 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- "K": Correspondence, orders, bills, invoices, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- "L": Correspondence, bills, orders, invoices, labor market letters, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- "Marine Midland": Correspondence, credit (interest due) slips, the Point of View, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- "Metropolitan Life": Correspondence, statistics, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 38)
- "Milligan & Higgins": Bills of lading, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- "M": Correspondence, orders, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- "N": Correspondence, orders, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- "NSRA [National Shoe Retailers Association]": Correspondence, bulletins, newsletters, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- "O": Correspondence, orders, accounts, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- "P.O. Box Rent, Ins. Registered Mail, Etc.": Receipts, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 44)
- "P": Correspondence, reports, orders, invoices, flyer, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 45)
- "R.J.P.": Apparently copy of speech or article, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- "Quotations": Correspondence, blueline drawing & layout for proposed extension to Wetstuck dryer, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- "Q": Correspondence, orders, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- "William Remlinger": Correspondence, orders, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- "Roselle Converting Company": Forms, correspondence, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 5)